房间很漂亮 真棒
Nice room, fancy.
还不错
It's not bad.
我进城就住在这儿 所以
I stay here whenever I'm in town, so...
真棒 宝贝
That's nice, baby.
现在 我们把烦人的外套脱掉
Now, let's get that silly jacket off.
也许
Maybe...
我赌50块他会临阵退缩
50 bucks says he chickens out.
不可能 他可是花了快一个月的薪水
No way. He just shelled out like a month's salary.
-他已经装弹上膛了 -他有点头大
- He's locked and loaded. - He's way over his head.
看看他有多不安
Look how fidgety he is.
这是他第一次找应召女郎
It's his first time with a working girl.
你还懂点读心术么
You're some kind of mind reader?
我们已经看过上百万条这种视频了
We've watched a million videos like this,
赋予了我烦人的洞察男性心理的能力
giving me disturbing insight into the male psyche.
我们进入正题吧
Let's get to business.
真的吗 哇哦
Really? Whoa...
不 等等
No, wait!
求你 你不必这样做
Please. You don't have to do this.
NCIS新奥尔良S03E13
是谁在那儿 亮出身份来
Whoever's there, identify yourself!
哦
Ow!
抱歉 是我
Sorry. It's me.
我是Sebastian
It's Sebastian.
第一天上班 有点儿兴奋
First day on the job, I got a little excited,
我睡不着 所以我想
I couldn't sleep, so I figured
直接过来吧
I'd just come in.
现在是凌晨五点
At 5:00 in the morning.
我觉得过来屡一下头绪
Thought I'd just get a head start on things,
或许放一下 我的东西
maybe unpack my stuff.
噢 我该把东西放哪儿
Anyway, where should I put my stuff?
桌子还没给你送来 还在运送中
I haven't gotten you a desk yet. Still figuring out logistics.
好的 好吧 没关系
Okay. All right, that's fine.
我就 呃
I'll just, uh...
我就先拿着这些东西
I'll just hold onto this for now.
我们会给你找个地儿放
We'll find a place for you.
哦 肯定的 是啊 没错 我知道
Oh, totally. Yeah, yeah. I know, I know.
只是 我很焦虑 你知道吗
Just, I'm so nervous, you know?
就像 第一天来学校你谁都不认识
Like, first day at school and you don't know anyone
那样的焦虑 不过这很奇怪 对吧
kind of nervous, but that's strange, right?
因为我 我认识这里的每一个人
'Cause I, I know everyone here.
进入新工作都不简单
Never easy taking a new job.
尤其在一个有经验的队伍
Especially on an experienced team.
但是你来这儿是有原因的
But you're here for a reason.
你会做得很好 我保证
You'll do great. I promise.
另外
And...
我有件东西
...I got something
要给你
for you.
你的配枪
Your service weapon.
欢迎来到NCIS
Welcome to NCIS.
法证探员Lund
Forensics Agent Lund.
这个
This is...
这真的发生了
this is really happening.
还有这个
So's this...
四具尸体 包括一名海军
Four dead bodies... Including a sailor.
是的 太棒了
Yes! All right.
伙计 这样太冷漠了 抱歉
Man, that's insensitive. I'm sorry.
只是作为探员的第一个案子 你懂吧
Just first case as an agent, you know?
是啊 会很棒的
Yeah. Gonna be great.
Annabelle Shaw上尉
Lieutenant Annabelle Shaw.
来自Belle Chase的电脑专家
Computer specialist out of Belle Chase.
海军派她来协助安装软件更新
Navy sent her here to help install a software update,
这是她的搭档 Eric Smith
along with her co-worker, Eric Smith.
国防部承包商
DoD contractor.
凶手或者凶手们穿过那扇门
Killer or killers come through that door,
开枪
guns blazing.
干掉了警卫
Takes out the guard,
Smith先生和Shaw上尉
Mr. Smith and Lt. Shaw?
这到底是什么地方
What exactly is this place?
-这是个联邦数据共享... -这是某种数据场地...
- It's a federal data sharing... - Well, some short of data farm...
抱歉 我 该我说吗
I'm sorry. Do--? Is it my turn?
只是想弄明白案件陈述礼节
Just trying to figure out the-the briefing etiquette.
说吧 我的朋友
Go for it, my friend.
好的 这是联邦服务器场
All right. It's a Federal server farm,
国防部和司法部的不同机构在这里分享和分析情报
where different agencies at DoD and DOJ share and analyze Intel.
没错 FBI CIA 海军情报部门
Yeah. FBI, CIA, Navy Intel--
所有这些部门都把他们的文件存在这儿
all of them store their files here.
高价值目标
High-value target.
可以假设数据已经被盗吗
Assuming data was stolen?
没错 根据记录日志 得有几十亿字节的信息被盗
Yeah. Over a thousand terabytes worth, according to this log.
我们面临的是国家安全的巨大漏洞
We're talking about a massive breach of national security.
哦 我有点儿接受不了
Oh! I just can't get over it.
嗷 你成长了呀
Aww. You're all grown up...
好了 行了 我要工作呢
Okay. All right. You know, I'm trying to work here.
哦对 是啊 当然
Oh, right. Yes, of course.
第四个受害人在外面
There's a fourth victim outside.
也是中了两枪
Also shot twice.
我们要找几个嫌疑人
How many suspects we looking at?
呃 现在下结论有点早
Uh, it's too soon to tell,
但我敢说就一个人
but I'd say just one.
每个受害人都是胸前中了两枪
Each victim has a double tap to the chest.
他对武器非常熟练
Someone was very handy with a weapon.
对电子设备也很熟悉
Handy with electronics, too.
整个安全系统 包括监控
Entire security system, including surveillance
都被离线攻破
is taken offline.
哦 很抱歉
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
还在试图搞清楚时机问题
Trying to work out the timing, still.
好吧 好的 所以我们得知可能是一个人
Okay. All right. So we've got what could be one man
闯了进来
who breaks in,
没被发现 杀了四个人
undetected, kills four,
还窃取了大量
steals massive amounts
敏感的政府数据
of sensitive government data.
可能是间谍行为
Probably espionage.
应该尽快跟国防部和司法部谈谈
Should talk to DoD and DOJ, ASAP.
没错 我让Sonja和Gregorio马上联系他们
Yeah. I'll have Sonja and Gregorio contact them now.
同时 Christopher 你去
In the meantime, Christopher. Let's start--
-让一下 -嗯 好
- excuse me - Hmm? Yeah.
从该地区其它楼栋
pulling surveillance footage
找一下监控录像
from other buildings in the area.
-没问题 -哦 我跟Lasalle一起去
- You got it. - Oh, I'll go with Lasalle.
不 不 不用 你不用去 你在这里
No, no, no. You're okay. You stay here.
跟Loretta一起工作 很多证据需要处理
Work with Loretta. Lot of evidence to process.
这是个好主意 而且不只是物理证据
That's a good idea. Not just physical evidence, either.
不论是谁干的 一定留下了数字痕迹
Whoever did this must've left a digital trace.
Patton出城去参加什么信息技术讨论会
Patton's out of town at some I.T. conference,
但我们或许应该联系一下他
but we should probably contact him.
好主意 现在就去做
Good idea. Do it now.
我们要在被盗数据落入敌手前
We need to find whoever did this
查出是谁干的
before the stolen data gets in the wrong hands.
看起来不太舒服
That just looks uncomfortable.
一切都好不自在
Everything about it.
我知道我们在NCIS比较随意
I know we keep it casual at NCIS,
但是看起来你们在拉低下限
but it seems like you're pushing it.
我们在工作呢
We're workin' here.
以为你们在联系国防部和司法部呢
Thought you were contacting DoD and DOJ.
两个部门都报告说两周前
Well, both agencies reported an attempted hack
有针对该机构的黑客攻击行为
of the facilities two weeks ago.
所以Shaw上尉被派来升级软件
That's why Lieutenant Shaw was sent here to update software,
增强网络防御能力
strengthen cyber defense.
知道谁是黑客吗
Any idea who the hacker was?
不知道 但我们猜测
None. But it's our guess,
和凶手是同一个人
it's the same person as the killer.
这是他窃取的部分内容
This is part of what he was stole.
FBI对一个
Surveillance from FBI
大型卖淫团伙的监控
of a major prostitution ring.
我认识他
I know him.
那是Long议员
It's Councilman Long.
你是怎么找到这个的
Well, how'd you find this?
我们没找 一小时前
We didn't. It went viral
它就在网络上扩散了
an hour ago.
一起被扩散的还有另外八个
A long with eight other videos
新奥尔良名人的视频
of prominent New Orleanians.
都是被盗文件的一部分
All a part of the stolen files.
每个目标都处于某种程度的
And each of our subjects are under some form
调查中
of investigation.
网上炸开了锅
Internet's blowing up.
视频有上千的点击量
Videos are getting thousands of hits.
这完全是公开羞辱
It's straight up public humiliation.
我听着不像间谍行为
Doesn't sound like espionage to me.
啊 嗨 新人呀
Ah, hey. It's the new guy.
我可以这么说 因为我已经来了一个星期
I can say that, 'cause I've been here a week.
欢迎加入 菜鸟
Welcome aboard, newbie.
你们有什么发现
You got something for us?
我在现场发现了一些上皮细胞
I'd say. Found epidermis cells
但与受害人不匹配
at the scene that didn't match any of our victims.
与之匹配的嫌疑人是
But they did match a very likely suspect.
Ethan Beck
Ethan Beck.
Ethan Beck?
好吧 你们听说过匿名者 对吧
So. All right. So you've heard of Anonymous, right?
当然
Of course.
很好 Ethan Beck和他的手下
Okay. Well, Ethan Beck and his people
比匿名者要强十倍 他们的任务
are, like, ten times better. And their mission
就是揭露所有的腐败
is to expose corruption wherever it is.
那我们在哪儿能找到这家伙
So where do we find this guy?
问题来了 你根本找不到他
Well, that's the thing. You don't really find him.
只有他来找你 他就像 一个幽灵
He finds you. He's like a... like a phantom.
我现在很期待"但是"这个词
I'm expecting a"but" right about now.
但是 几个礼拜以前
But there was a failed hack attempt on the facility
有未遂黑客攻击行为
a couple weeks back...
Patton已经找出
And Patton was able to find out
黑客入侵的位置
where that hack came from.
我现在就把具体细节发给你
And I'm gonna send you those details right now.
在庞恰特雷恩湖的一家废弃餐馆
The abandoned restaurant on Lake Pontchartrain.
事实上 IP地址现在还处于活跃状态
Yeah. Actually, there's activity on the I.P. address right now.
现在还有人在那儿
Somebody's still there.
可能是凶手
Could be our killer.
Gregorio 你和我一起
Gregorio, you're with me.
海军罪案调查处
NCIS!
举起手来 让我们看见
Hands where we can see 'em.
慢点
Slow!
Elvis
Elvis!
Dwayne Pride
Dwayne Pride.
世界上有那么多城镇 城镇里又有那么多酒馆 瞧
Of all the gin joints in all the towns, and look,
你还带上了小伙计
you brought your little buddy with you, too.
早该猜到的
Should've guessed,
要是我们有黑客的工作 肯定让你来做
if we had a major hack job, we'd run into you.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
这看上去对我很不利
This looks really bad for me.
但这次我发誓 不是我干的
but this time I swear I did not do it.
好吧
Right.
把手放到我能看到的地方
Hands where I can see 'em.
我有种强烈的似曾相识的感觉
I am having a raging bout of déjà vu right now.
Dwayne 告诉她我并不危险
Dwayne, tell her I'm not dangerous.
上次我们和你打交道的时候 你带着武器
Last time we dealt with you, you were armed
还差点射中一个女人
and almost shot a woman.
她说得没错 Elvis
She's got a point, Elvis.
不考虑具体情况 不公平
Out of context, unfair.
当时是那女人冲着我枪口来的
And that woman sort of had it coming.
请问 我能把他铐起来吗
Can I cuff him, please?
还不行 纽约人
Not yet, New York.
Elvis 这家餐馆
Elvis, this restaurant
是一个黑客入侵
was the source of a hack attempt
联邦服务器场的源头
on a Federal server farm.
今天早上 4个人在那儿被害
A facility where four people were killed this morning.
好吧 那么你认为
Right. So you think it's, uh,
我在这里很可疑
suspicious that I'm here,
考虑到我过去一些
considering my past miscommunications
与法律相抵触的行为
with the law.
嗯 与法律相抵触 你是说
Um, by miscommunications, do you mean
多项重罪判决吗 没错
multiple felony convictions? Then, yes.
我不是你要找的罪犯
I'm not the felon you're looking for.
罪犯叫Ethan Beck
His name is Ethan Beck.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know that?
因为我也在找他
'Cause I'm looking for him, too.
他管理着一个被称为"集结者"的黑客行动主义小组
He runs a hacktivist group called the "Collective".
更像是恐怖组织
More like a terrorist organization,
曝光个人丑闻
exposing people's dirty secrets.
不 创立集结者是为了增加透明度
No. The Collective was founded to create transparency
和曝光腐败
and expose corruption.
那么 现在它在曝光
Well, right now, it's exposing
名人的私生活
prominent folks' personal lives.
是啊 这让我非常恼火
Yeah, and that's really pissing me off.
你为什么会在意
Why do you care?
因为我的名声要被败坏了
Because my reputation's at stake.
因为他是集结者的创始人
Because he created the Collective.
没错 我和Ethan一起建立的
Yeah. I created it with Ethan.
他是我的门生
He was my protégé.
但他很自负
But he let his ego get the best of him,
这个组织也偏离了原来的目的
and it's not about the cause anymore.
变成了Ethan证明自身强大的工具
It's about Ethan proving how powerful he is.
因此你们一定要让我帮忙找到他
And that's why you guys have to let me help you find him.
谈到自负 我们能处理这事 对吧
Talk about ego. We can handle this, all right?
Dwayne 你不知道你在和谁打交道
Dwayne, you don't have any idea who you're dealing with.
对吧 他很难追踪 听着
Do you? He's hard to track. Listen.
他搞垮了世界500强企业
He's taken down Fortune 500 companies.
他让政府部门束手无策
He's brought government agencies to their knees.
而且他从来没被抓到过
And he's never been caught.
他很危险
He's dangerous.
Elvis Ethan Beck杀了4个人
Elvis, Ethan Beck murdered four people,
包括一个海军上尉 我们知道他很危险
including a Navy Lieutenant. We know he's dangerous.
说得好
Good point.
但你得让我帮你们找到他
But you got to let me help you find him.
他所有的伎俩都是我教的
I taught him every trick he knows.
我是唯一
I am the one guy
能追踪到他的人
who could track this dude down.
求你了
Please.
-Gregorio -在
- Gregorio? - Yeah?
把Elvis带回NCIS
Take Elvis back to NCIS.
备齐所有他需要的东西
Set up him up with whatever he needs.
当真么
For real?
别那么沮丧
Don't look so upset.
我不咬人
I don't bite.
除非你恳请我这么做
Unless you ask real nice.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
市长召唤我
Summoned by the mayor.
Douglas Hamilton市长
Mayor Douglas Hamilton...
他们截获了我的电子邮件 Dwayne
They got my e-mails, Dwayne.
-你有没有 -他们截获我的电子邮件
Do you...? They got my e-mails!
明白吗 还放到网上
All right? Posted them online.
无数条私人信息
Hundreds of private messages.
你只是其中的一个
You're not the only one.
少来 记者一直追问
Come on, the reporters asking Que--
他们无处不在 你也瞧见了 对吧
They're all over the place. You've seen them, right?
和你的新闻秘书举止亲密
...intimately involved with your press secretary.
呃 我没有什么好说的
Uh, I have nothing to say...
没有人来
I've got nobody, though,
替我挡下这些问题
to field questions for me,
因为我的新闻秘书的丈夫
because my press secretary's
让她辞职了
husband made her resign.
我有大量凶杀案要解决
I've got multiple homicides to solve,
能说重点吗
can we cut to the chase?
你倒是很开心啊 不是吗
You're enjoying this, ain't ya?
我看得出来
I can see.
幸灾乐祸 有那么一点儿
You're enjoying this, just a little bit.
市长先生 你的重点是
Your point, Mr. Mayor?
我知道你认为我是个坏人
Now, I know you think that I'm a bad guy.
对吧 呃
Right? That, uh...
我只在乎自己
I'm only interested in myself.
如果按过往来说的话
If history is any guide.
我搞砸了 Dwayne 我完了
I'm screwed, Dwayne. Oh, yeah. I'm done.
这件事我无能为力
And there's nothing I can do about that now,
但是无辜的人正受到伤害
but innocent people are getting hurt.
人们的私生活被曝光
Private lives are getting exposed.
对很多好人来说会很糟
And this could be very bad for a lot of good people.
我们都认同这点 对吧
We agree on that much, don't we?
我对你有用
I can be useful to you.
我可以幕后操控
I can pull strings.
若你需要 我可以为你提供资源
I could give you access to resources if you need them.
无论你要什么 尽管说
Whatever you need. Just say the word.
我们一起来解决
Let's fix this together.
也许有些事你能做
Might be something you can do.
呃 你
Uh... you...
你是
you're, uh...
我是说
I mean...
你中风了吗
Are you having a stroke, kid?
说真的 要我给你做人工呼吸吗
Seriously, do I have to give you mouth to mouth?
我是Elvis
I'm Elvis.
哦 是的 我知道你是谁
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know exactly who you are.
你是人民英雄
You're-you're a personal hero.
希望这听起来不奇怪
I hope that doesn't sound strange.
没有 一点也不奇怪
No, no, that's not creepy at all.
只是 你的事迹是我
It's just, your work is pretty much the reason
最初接触电脑的主要原因
I got into computers in the first place.
好吧 现在我感觉自己老了 但也有点荣幸
Okay, now I feel old, but also a bit flattered.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我在试着追踪Ethan Beck
I'm trying to track down Ethan Beck.
抱歉 我不知道这是你的办公室
Sorry, I didn't know this is your office,
因为你这儿有黑客设备
but you got a killer setup here.
是的 黑客入侵用的设备 但不是我的
Oh, yeah, it is killer, but it's not mine.
我本身没有办公室
I don't really have an office, per Se.
-我是新人 -好吧
- I-I'm kind of new. - Okay.
事实上 我刚来
Actually, I'm very new.
虽然我以前经常来
Although, I've also been around a lot,
所以 这很复杂
so, it's all very complicated.
总之 我也要找Ethan Beck
Anyway, I'm-I'm supposed to find Ethan Beck, too.
好吧 坐下吧
Okay, good. Cop a squat.
让我们找到他
Let's get at it.
好的
All right.
额 用那个吧
Um, uh, over there's good.
-好的 -是 是
- That's probably good. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ethan很难追踪 你知道吧
Now, Ethan is a hard guy to track down, you know?
没那么容易能追踪到 但是 我们有办法
Not easy to trace, but, uh, we got a work-around here.
我们能看到整个城市的网络通信量
We got all the Internet traffic for the entire city.
哇哦 你是怎么...
Whoa, how did you...?
不是我 是你们市长
Not me, your mayor.
他和雇员睡觉抽空来给我们帮忙
He took a break from bedding his employees to help us out.
多亏了你老板
Thanks to your boss.
所以 如果Ethan要筛选这些偷来的文件
So... so, if Ethan's sifting through all these stolen files,
并把它们放到网上 那么他会需要
and he's posting them online, then he's gonna need
占用大量带宽 对吗
a high concentration of bandwidth, right?
是的 而且Ethan不会做这苦差事的
Right, and Ethan doesn't do the grunt work,
所以会有个喽啰替他做
so one of his minions does it for him.
所以 如果我们找到这低段位的菜鸟
So, if we trace the low-hanging fruit...
顺藤摸瓜就能钓到大鱼
We can trade up to the big dog.
对的
That's right.
太好了 真有趣
All right. Yeah! This is fun.
是的 是的 继续干活
Yeah, yeah, eyes front. Yeah.
好的
Okay.
在法国区的咖啡馆
I've got some heavy traffic
发现了大流量的传输
coming from a coffee shop in The Quarter.
干得好 孩子 召唤骑兵吧
Good job, kid. Call in the cavalry.
事实上 我就是骑兵
Actually, I am the cavalry.
等等 我需要你 帮我找到其它集结者
Actually, I need you to help me find the other Collectives.
好啊 好啊
Oh, okay, yeah.
- 开工吧 -好 来吧
- Let's do it. - Yeah. Right.
-在那儿 我是说 -回到这里 当然
- By here, I mean of course... - Back over there. Sure.
我这就给Lasalle打电话
I'm gonna call Lasalle.
肯定在电话那头等着呢
Pretty much always over there.
真是太好了
Oh, this is great.
就像蝙蝠侠和罗宾 只是罗宾更牛逼些
Like Batman and Robin, except a cooler Robin.
咖啡店在那个转角
Coffee shop's up here on the corner.
现在确认了
It's official.
市长Hamilton的不雅视频已经传开了
Mayor Hamilton's sex tape just went wide.
他们抓到他和新闻秘书有一腿
They got him with his press secretary.
不 是其他人 朋友的老婆
No. Someone else. A friend's wife.
- 我真替他们难过啊 -替Hamilton吗
- I feel bad. - For Hamilton?
他和那个女人 任何隐私被侵犯的人
For him, the woman, anybody who has their privacy invaded.
我是说 我们都有隐私 不是吗
I mean, we all have secrets, no?
不是每个人
Not everyone.
同意
Agreed.
好吧 你们真是一对圣人
Okay, you got a couple of saints here.
如果你生活正派 就没什么可隐藏
Well, you live a decent life, you got nothing to hide.
看看那个机器人先生
Check out Mr. Robot.
对 莫霍克人 人体穿环
Yeah, Mohawk, piercings,
可能是我们要找的人
could be our guy.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
联邦探员
Federal agents.
需要问你几个问题
Need to ask you a few questions.
兔子要跑了
We got a rabbit.
-抓到你了 -放开我
- Easy now. - Get off me.
亚提卡 亚提卡
【注：在1971年亚提卡监狱暴动事件中，
政府不当的处理方式（射杀42人）
引发了美国社会一次巨大的风波】
Attica! Attica!
还是让女士们搞定吧
I'm gonna let you ladies handle this one.
谢谢你 Roy
Thank you, Roy.
你有麻烦了 Aviva
You're in a lot of trouble, Aviva.
袭击联邦探员
Assaulting a Federal agent.
是你们先对我动粗的
Your guy manhandled me.
你还有个大的麻烦
You got bigger problems.
我们知道你与
We know that you're connected
联邦机构的主要安全漏洞有牵扯
to a major security breach at a Federal facility.
你公开了很多敏感数据
That you've released sensitive data to the public.
你是集结者的一员
You're a member of the Collective,
而且你为Ethan Beck工作
and you work for Ethan Beck.
证据
Prove it.
我们想要知道的一切
Everything we need to know
就在你的电脑里
is right here in your computer.
启动它啊
Boot it up.
试试进入硬盘
Try and access the hard drive.
看看会发生什么
See what happens.
陷阱 是吗
Booby trapped, huh?
哈
Wow.
真聪明
Smart.
聪明到
At a level you can't even
你根本来不及思考
begin to contemplate.
集结者不惧法律
The Collective isn't afraid of laws
或后果 或警察
or consequences or cops.
可以了
That's fair enough.
但现在 我不是你要担心的人
But... I'm not the one you need to worry about right now.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我是Elvis Bertrand
I'm Elvis Bertrand.
不可能
No way.
你的噩梦现在变成了现实
And your worst nightmare is coming true in real time,
因为我不在乎法律或是规矩
because I don't care about laws or rules
或是你硬盘里可悲的陷阱
or pathetic booby traps on your hard drive.
你要配合我们工作
You are gonna cooperate with us,
不然我就将你所做的一切
or I'm gonna expose every move you've made
都作为所谓的黑客行动主义者
as a so-called hacktivist
公之于众
to the whole world.
你们想要什么
What do you want?
想要你联系Ethan Beck
Want you to contact Ethan Beck.
只需要联系到他 剩下的我们来处理
Just reach out to him, and I will do the rest.
好了
Okay.
我希望你知道你在做什么
I hope you know what you're doing,
因为他不喜欢被人找到
'cause he doesn't like to be found.
现在 我只是在运行一个
Now, I'm just running
我设计的 小小的优雅的回溯程序
a little, elegant, backtrace program I devised,
它会在他发现之前攻击他的电脑
and it will attack his computer before he knows what hit him.
喔
Ooh.
不太妙啊
That's not good.
Elvis
Elvis.
知道怎么回事吗
Any idea what's going on?
不是我干的 我发誓
I did not do it. I swear.
不是你做的 是Ethan
You didn't do this. Ethan did.
我听说你在找我
I heard you were looking for me.
你能追踪到他的地址吗
Can you trace his location?
我试试 但是他已经控制了我们整个网络
I'll try, but he's got control of our whole network.
你已经捅了马蜂窝
You've uncovered the hornet's nest
吵醒了一个沉睡的巨人
and woken a sleeping giant.
好吧 我不管你这极其夸张的
Okay, I'm gonna ignore your agregious overuse
混合隐喻 Ethan
of mixed metaphors, Ethan,
想问你 "你到底哪根筋不对了 伙计"
and ask you, "What the hell is your problem, buddy?!"
Elvis 你背叛了我们的事业
Elvis, you're a traitor to the cause.
我拒绝和你谈话
I refuse to speak to you.
你杀害了四个人的正当理由是什么
What cause justifies the murder of four people?
我不想听你瞎说
I won't listen to your lies.
你完全不知道你在说些什么
You have no idea what you're talking about
或你正在和谁说话
or who you're messing with.
-Sebastian -他是怎么办到的
- Sebastian! - How is he doing that?
我不知道 但真的很酷炫
I don't know, but it's kind of cool.
好吧 Ethan Ethan 听我说 伙计
Okay, Ethan, Ethan, listen to me, buddy.
你不是这样的人
This isn't you.
我要你过来
I need you to come in here.
别再找我
Stop looking for me.
抱歉 我们办不到
Sorry, we can't oblige you of that.
那你们就为此付出代价吧
Then you'll all pay for it.
好吧 呃
Okay, well...
不该这么糟糕
that could've gone better.
这个绿野仙踪似的举动
This whole Wizard of Oz act doesn't exactly mesh
和杀掉四个人的冷血杀手不太吻合
with a suspect willing to kill four people in cold blood.
这些疑问等我们找到他再说
Well, contradiction we can try to explain after we find him.
拜托 告诉我 你还有其它追踪Ethan Beck的方法吗
Please, tell me you have another way of tracing Ethan Beck?
没什么办法
Not off the top of my head.
他潜伏得很深
He's gone deep underground,
或许把电源插头都拔了
probably unplugging completely.
所以我们不能用数码追踪他
So we don't trace him digitally.
反正我们没办法在线上打败他
Never gonna outsmart him online, anyway.
哦 这么说好伤我心啊
Ooh, that hurts my feelings.
应该关注他在现实生活中的样子
Focus on who he is in the real world instead.
你是在说生活模式吗
You're talking about pattern of life?
额 这个"生活模式"是什么
Um, what is this "pattern of life"?
人物描绘技术
Profiling technique.
我们会收集关于疑犯的所有信息
We gather every detail we know about a suspect.
他吃什么 穿什么
What he eats, what he wears,
喜欢什么类型的音乐
kind of music he likes.
尤其是不寻常的事情
Especially irregularities.
任何不平常的特征或习惯
Any unusual traits or habits.
好吧 从何开始
Okay, where to start?
这个人只是在家里
Well, you got a guy that sits
坐在电脑屏幕前
alone at home in front of a computer screen.
怪人有自己的活动区域
Weirdness comes with the territory.
我们会把所有信息输入到分析程序里
We put it all into an analytical program,
然后会得到可以找到他的重要线索
and then we got a good shot at finding him.
你们真的认为这样有用吗
And you actually think that'll work?
不久前我们就是这么查到你的
We tracked your sorry ass not too long ago.
你要知道 如果当时你朝我开了枪 我们可能会成为朋友
You know, I think if you gave me a shot, we could become pals.
-真的吗 -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
以后再看有没有这可能
We're about to find out.
Elvis 和Gregorio谈谈
Elvis, sit with Gregorio.
关于Ethan的一切都告诉她
Tell her everything she needs to know about Ethan.
好了 来电了
Okay. Got the power going.
网络正在启动备份
The Internet's booting back up,
所以总而言之 可以正常运转了
so all in all, we're in business.
干得好 Sebastian
Good work, Sebastian.
Loretta有发现 所以 Sebastian
Loretta's got something, so, Sebastian,
你跟我一起 出发
you're with me. Let's go.
抱歉 失陪了
Sorry, excuse me.
说实话 我有点怕你
I'm gonna be honest. I'm a little afraid of you.
只是有一点么
Just a little?
你得学习一下怎么接受别人的称赞
You got to learn to take a compliment.
等等 这些邮件是什么
Wait, what are all these e-mails?
出故障还是怎么了
Some kind of glitch or something?
那些不是你的邮件
Those aren't your e-mails.
Ethan动作挺快啊
That Ethan sure works fast.
做什么的动作挺快
Works fast at what?
在制造混乱方面
At-at creating chaos.
呦 有网络了
Yo, the Internet's back up.
我知道
I know.
我刚收到一大堆邮件
I just got a crazy amount of e-mails.
是啊 我也一样 似乎不太好
Yeah, me, too, and it's not good.
是你做卧底期间的ATF档案
These are ATF files from your undercover days.
哇哦 你开玩笑吗 怎么回事啊
Whoa. Are you kidding me? How'd that happen?
我猜是Ethan Beck
Well, I'm assuming it's Ethan Beck
在兑现他的承诺
making good on his threat.
好吧 你得删了这些东西
Well, you need to get rid of those.
对啊 我这里全都是
Yeah, I'm all over it.
嗨 你最好也清理一下
Hey, and you might want to do the same
你的收件箱
with whatever's in your inbox.
没错
Yeah.
虽然我不是很想说
但是我非常不确定Percy合适加入团队 King
我们再谈谈吧
是啊 我应该清理一下
Yeah, I probably should have.
哦 天呐
Oh, boy.
你发现什么了
What'd you get?
只是一封你发给Pride的邮件
Just an e-mail from you to Pride
里面说你认为我不该加入团队
saying that you don't think I should be added to the team.
你的卧底身份刚刚暴露
Your undercover identity was just exposed
而你就因为一个断章取义的邮件
and you're pissed about an e-mail
对我发火吗
taken completely out of context?
哦 拜托 告诉我怎么回事
Oh, by all means, give me the context.
这个嘛 我当时并不了解你 也不知道
Well, I didn't know you yet, and couldn't tell
你会怎样适应团队的机动性
how you would mix with the team dynamic.
我为团队挨过子弹 这表现怎样
I took a bullet for the team. How's that for dynamic?
我知道 你从那以后上百次的证明了自己
And you proved yourself a hundred times since, to me.
我也向你证明了我自己 对吗
And me to you, right?
我们也许应该在其他人受到伤害前
We should probably stop reading these
停止阅读这些邮件了
before someone else gets hurt.
既然Sebastian忙着发动网络战争
Well, since Sebastian's busy waging cyber-warfare,
我另找了一位技术员来分析
I had another tech analyze the bullets
Shaw上尉谋杀案的子弹
from Lieutenant Shaw's murder.
那些弹片都碎掉了
Well, those slugs were in fragments.
你还进行弹道匹配么
You were able to get a ballistics match?
没有 是更有趣的方法
No, something far more intriguing:
墨水的痕迹
traces of ink.
墨水 什么样的墨水
Ink? What kind of ink?
打印机 钢笔 我是说 大概有
Printer, pen? I mean, there's
几百种分类吧
literally hundreds of classifications.
我不知道 Sebastian 因为样本太小
I don't know, Sebastian, but the sample was so small,
除你之外 我不想让任何人接触
I wouldn't want anyone to touch it, except you.
说得好
That's a good call.
玩毛细电泳法可不能太脆弱
Capillary electrophoresis is not for the faint of heart.
Ethan Beck正在证明他既危险又难以捉摸
This Ethan Beck is proving to be as elusive as he is dangerous.
他让我们大吃一惊
He threw us all for a loop.
我可从未见Elvis怕过谁
And I've never seen Elvis afraid of anyone.
担心Beck会回来 开枪杀人
Worried Beck will come back, guns blazing.
我怕的不只是枪
It's not just guns I'm afraid of here.
丑闻吗
A scandal then?
比如Hamilton市长的丑闻
Like with Mayor Hamilton?
To：NCIS总部--主任
个人意见关于Sebastian探员申请的回复
尽管他智商过人、勇于担当以及态度积极。
但我仍然担心Lund在这一领域的能力。
在他成为探员这方面仍然需要更多的观察。
这个 不只是他
Well, not just him.
现在新奥尔良的人都因为Ethan Beck
A lot of New Orleanians are reeling today
而头疼
because of Ethan Beck.
我要去 呃 我的实验室处理这个
I'm gonna go, uh, process this in my lab.
不用等我 这样你不用担心我
No need to wait, which should come as a relief to you,
在外勤方面没有经验
since you won't have to worry about
这对你应该是个解脱
my inability in the field for a while.
好吧 那是什么意思
Okay, what was that about?
不知道
Not a clue.
屋漏偏逢连阴雨
Rains, it pours.
Hamilton市长再次陷入水深火热之中
Mayor Hamilton is once again in hot water.
一段市长和一位未知女性的
A sex tape featuring the mayor
性爱录像被放到了网上
and an unidentified woman has been released online...
他们拿到了录像 Dwayne
They got videos, Dwayne.
我
Of me
跟不同的女人
with different women.
都是雇员吗
More staffers?
目前这不是重点 对吧
Well, that's not the point now, is it?
录像从哪儿来的
Why the hell is there video?
不知道
Couldn't say.
不知道还是不想说
Couldn't or won't?
我的邮件在联邦执法机构的数据库里
My e-mails are on a Federal law enforcement database.
好吧
Okay.
当今年代 这种事情时有发生
This day and age, that happens.
我们接受
We live with it.
但是录像
But the video--
那就意味着我
well, that means that I'm...
实际上是在被调查 对吗
actively under investigation, right?
我没调查你 如果你想问这个
I'm not investigating you, if that's your question.
没 至少目前没有
Not... currently, at least.
你对我做出过不少指控
Well, you've thrown a lot of accusations my way.
你知道 最近一次 Javier Garcia案件
You know, the Javier Garcia case, most recently.
Garcia被谋杀了 你知道的
Garcia was murdered. You know that.
但是
But,
如果有些事情
if there's something specific
你想坦白 我听着呢
you want to confess, I'm all ears.
好了 Dwayne
Well, Dwayne,
如果说这一天证明了什么
if this day has proven anything,
那就是每个人都有秘密 即便是你
it's that everybody has a secret, even you.
如果有人有目标地深入调查
And if someone were motivated to look hard enough,
谁知道他们会发现什么
who knows what they would find?
好吧
Here we go.
听着 你看到就是看到了
Look, you've seen what you've seen.
你又不能收回
You can't take it back.
这就是你的回答吗
That's your response?
你告诉Isler我们是毒贩派来的一对卧底
You told Isler we were a pair of cartel imbeds.
我说的是有可能
I said it was possible!
你还说我们睡在一起 恶心
And that we were sleeping together? Ew!
我说的只是感觉 诚实地讲
Look, you got a vibe, that's all I'm saying. Honestly?
很明显 你们没看看你们自己么
It's kind of obvious. Have you watched yourselves?
没 但是你看过
No, but you have.
监控我们好几个周 还拍照
Been surveilling us for weeks, taking photos.
这正是FBI把我送来的原因
That's why the FBI brought me here,
来调查你们 你们知道的
to investigate you. You know that!
是啊 可那是我们的私人生活
Yeah, but that's our personal lives.
你能确定哪些监控是必要的吗
Do you know what surveillance entails?
而且反正 我证明了你们的清白 所以
And I cleared you both anyways, so...
哦 我感觉好多了
Oh, I feel so much better.
很好 那现在我们可以谈谈我发现了什么
Good! 'Cause now we can talk about what I got.
你觉得我们...
What about what we...?
够了
Enough!
你们知道
You understand
这正是Ethan Beck想要的结果
this is exactly what Ethan Beck wants.
让我们退出游戏 迷惑自己
Throw us off our game, confuse us.
这样他就逃掉了 你们要让这事发生吗
So he can get away. You gonna let that happen?
那叫幸灾乐祸
It's called Shadenfreude.
当然
I'll say.
那是我几年前设计用来追踪
It's an algorithm I created years ago
多嘴的CEO们的算法
to go after mouthy CEOs.
它挑选邮件
It culls e-mails,
寻找与同事有关的敏感信息
looking for sensitive information about coworkers.
我设计它是用来揭露腐败
And I created it to expose corruption.
但是Ethan用它来对付你们
But Ethan has used it on you guys.
确定他的位置 有进展吗
Any progress locating him?
我们汇总了能找到的
We aggregated every detail we can find
关于Ethan Beck私人习惯和癖好的所有细节
on Ethan Beck's personal habits and idiosyncrasies.
信息很多 他恐高
There's a lot. He's afraid of heights,
所以他不会住在高层
so he's not living in a high-rise.
他还是个处于恢复期的瘾君子
He's also a recovering heroin addict,
我相信他没法跑太远
a big believer in the twelve steps.
好的 那他得离交易场所近一些
Okay, so he needs to be near meetings.
然后再加上
And then you add to that,
他是一个领地偏执狂
the paranoia that goes with the territory,
以强势人物为目标
going after the very powerful.
他富于机动性
He likes mobility,
一定在一个能立即逃跑的地方
has to be able to escape at a moment's notice.
好的 在这里
Okay, well around here,
水路是最快的逃跑方式 所以 是在一条船上
water's the fastest way out, so, a boat.
好了 我们怎样进一步缩小范围呢
Okay, how do we narrow it further?
披萨
Pizza.
Ethan痴迷于木烤箱披萨
Ethan is obsessed with wood oven pizza.
他一定要保证能随时订餐
And he has to have it delivered at all hours.
我们找到了
We got a hit.
贝壳海滩码头
Shell Beach Marina.
Gregorio 跟我一起
Gregorio, with me.
开始行动
Let's move.
高速互联网卫星
High-speed Internet satellite.
就是这里
This is the place.
NCIS 把手放在我能看见的地方 马上
NCIS, hands where I can see 'em, right now.
注射器
Syringe.
Pride 你得看看这个
Pride, you need to see this!
遗书
Suicide note.
这个家伙正忙于
This guy's in the middle of a crusade,
揭发他人
exposing people left and right
然后突然了结了自己
and just offs himself?
你看这事正常吗
Does that seem right to you?
这里的一切似乎都不正常
Nothing about this seems right.
Ethan Beck的血管里
Ethan Beck had a hundred milligrams
有一百毫克的高纯度海洛因
of nearly pure heroin in his bloodstream.
没人能给自己注射那么多
No one would have been able to inject that much.
在完成注射前他就会晕倒
He would have passed out before completing the dose.
这个人是被谋杀的
This man was murdered.
然而有人希望我们认为他是自杀
Yet someone wants us to think he committed suicide.
你觉得他有同伙吗
You think he had an accomplice?
Beck也许可以在网上发布
Beck may have released confidential files
机密文件和录像
and videos on the Internet,
黑进我们的电子邮箱
thrown my team into disarray
让我的团队陷入混乱
by hacking our e-mails,
但是攻破一个联邦机构
but breaching a federal facility?
还熟练地杀掉我们四个人
And expertly killing four people?
没错 Beck先生身体不是很健康
Yeah, Mr. Beck was not in the pink of health.
他起身开门都会气喘吁吁
He would have gotten winded answering the front door,
更别说闯入大门
let alone storming the gates.
那么 到底怎么回事
Well then, what?
有人把Ethan的DNA留在犯罪现场
Someone planted Ethan's DNA at our crime scene?
栽赃他让他做替罪羊吗
Set him up to take the fall?
为什么搞得这么麻烦
Why go to all that trouble?
Elvis和队里其他人
Elvis and the rest of the team
正在搜索Ethan的电脑
are searching through Ethan's computer right now
看能不能找到答案
for the answer,
可能他们又互相吵了起来
provided they aren't at each other's throats again.
嗯 团队成员还有矛盾吗
Mm. Still dissention in the ranks?
说实话 我很吃惊 只要这么一件小事
Honestly, I'm surprised how little it took
就能把我们踢出局
to throw us off our game.
没人被踢出局 Dwayne
No one's off their game, Dwayne.
我们是家人 家人之间争吵很正常
We're family, families bicker.
哦 Pride 没想到你在这里
Oh, Pride, I didn't realize you were here.
我正要打电话告诉你一些信息
I was about to call you with some information.
好啊 我在这呢
Well, here I am.
你发现什么了
What do you got?
我分析了从Shaw上尉体内子弹上
Well, I analyzed the ink found on the bullet
发现的墨水
from Lieutenant Shaw's body.
结果发现
Turns out,
那是用来纹身的
it's tattoo ink.
是一种被称作"Chimera"的特殊专利配方
Special proprietary blend called "Chimera"
限量供应 而且
Sold in limited supply and only used
这一地区只有一家店在使用
by one shop in the area.
我猜你会带一个更有经验的探员
Guessing you're gonna take one of your more experienced agents
跟你一起去查个明白
to go check it out.
我猜
And I'm guessing
你现在的行为
your behavior right now
跟我在邮件里说过的什么话有关
is about something I said in an e-mail.
说出来吧
Out with it!
你跟NCIS主任说我经验不足
You told the director of NCIS that I was inexperienced
而且你对我的外勤能力缺乏信心
and that you're unsure of my ability in the field.
是的 因为你确实经验不足
That's right. Because you are inexperienced,
Sebastian 而且你还没出勤几次
Sebastian. And you haven't been out in the field that much,
但你知道我还说了什么吗
but you know what else I said?
我愿意打赌 如果给你一个机会
I'd be willing to bet you'd make a fantastic agent
-你会成为一个出色的探员 -哦
- if given a chance. - Oh.
这个 我 我猜他们没把完整的邮件发给我
Well, I-I guess they didn't send the whole e-mail then.
没错
Exactly.
现在你知道了
So, now you know.
我们可否去纹身店呢
May we please go to the tattoo parlor?
好啊
Yeah.
Chimera墨水 没错 我想我几个月前买过一些
Chimera ink? Yeah, I think I bought some a few months ago.
有些游客想带点新奥尔良特色回家
Up sell it to the tourists when they want to
我会卖一些
bring a part of New Orleans home with them.
几乎没用过
Barely ever use it.
能看看你的存货吗
Can we see your supply?
为什么
Why?
这跟一起正在进行的调查有关
It's in connection with an ongoing investigation.
在里屋的什么地方 你知道 我不是很...
It's somewhere in the back room, you know, I don't really have...
哦 不用担心 我会找出来的
Oh, don't worry, I-I can go check it out.
等等 等一下 伙计
Wait, hold on, man.
我按特定的方式整理的物品 好吗
I got it organized in a very particular way, all right?
-让我来找给你看 -好了 等等
- I'll just show you. - Okay, all right,
听着 我还有几个问题想先问你
look, I still have a few more questions for you first.
Sebastian 去吧
Sebastian, go ahead.
你见过这个人吗
You ever seen this man?
这也叫整理
This is organized?
哦 嗨 伙计 抱歉
Oh, hey, man, I'm sorry.
我没意识到你在这里
I-I didn't realize you were there.
哦 没事 哥们儿
Yeah, no worries, man.
补觉呢 哈
Catching some Z's, huh?
晚上没睡好是吗
Rough night?
可以这么说
You could say that.
呃 你能不能帮我找一下
Uh, any chance that you could help me
Chimera在哪儿
find the Chimera?
找什么
The what now?
墨水
The ink.
哦 对 好 没问题
Oh, right. Yeah, sure.
Chimera 是的
Chimera. Yeah.
我来帮你找 好的
I'll help you look. Okay.
我猜 呃 多数人喜欢在晚上纹身 是吧
I imagine, uh, most people get tattoos at night, huh?
一般人不会大清早一起床
It's not often you wake up first thing in the morning
就说 嗨 "我想在前胸纹一个
and saying, "Hey, I want a naked lady riding a dragon
骑着龙的裸女"
across my chest."
是啊 听起来没错
Yeah, sounds about right.
你在找这个 对吗
Looking for this, right?
哦 对 太棒了 谢谢你
Uh, yeah. That's great, thank you.
我想请你让一下
I'm just gonna ask you to move out of my way...
-不可以 -好吧
- Yeah, I can't do that. - Okay.
实际上这不是个请求 我是个联邦探员
It's not really a request. See, I'm a Federal Agent.
Sebastian
Sebastian!
你还好吗
You all right?
我想那就是凶手
I think it was the killer.
他拿着枪 往后门跑了
He got a gun, he went out the back.
从纹身店
Pulled DNA
提取了DNA
from the tattoo parlor,
确认我们嫌疑人的身份是Damon Yang
identified our suspect as Damon Yang.
他加入了七鹰三合会
He's affiliated with the Seven Eagles Triad.
他们在上海和旧金山都有基地
They're based in Shanghai and San Francisco,
Damon就是从那儿来的
where Damon is from originally.
看起来他过去几个月一直在新奥尔良
Looks like he's been in New Orleans the past few months.
平时躲在纹身店里 伺机出动
Holing up at a tattoo shop and Triad front.
纹身店经理与他们无关
The manager of the shop's not affiliated.
对七鹰的勾当毫不知情
Knows nothing about Seven Eagles business.
那是因为七鹰本来就没什么勾当
That's because there is no Seven Eagles business.
FBI去年搜捕过他们
The FBI busted them last year.
端掉了他们整个领导层
Shut down their entire leadership.
包括Damon的父亲 Derek Yang
Including Damon's father, Derek Yang.
Damon和Ethan Beck有什么关联
What's the connection between Damon and Ethan Beck?
看起来没有任何关系
There doesn't seem to be one.
除了他是个网络犯罪专家
Except for the fact that he specializes in cyber crimes,
身份窃贼 信用卡诈骗犯
identity theft, credit card fraud.
他很厉害
He was prodigious.
看他脖子上的纹身
And look at his neck tat.
438.
三合会用数字代码来区分他们的级别
Triads use numeric codes to distinguish their ranks.
你有什么发现么
Mean something to you?
我一直在浏览集结者的留言板
Well, I was looking through the Collective message boards
寻找其他嫌疑人
for other suspects.
那儿确实有个人的昵称是 438
There was someone whose handle was “438”"
你觉得Damon是集结者成员么
Thinking Damon was a Collective member, too?
可能他为了接近Ethan Beck而加入的
Maybe he joined up to get close to Ethan Beck.
他们一起攻入了
They worked together on breaching
那座联邦服务器场
the Federal server farm.
然后在文件被盗以后 他杀死了Beck
Then he kills Beck after the files were stolen?
他在追查什么
What was he after?
Elvis在研究Ethan的电脑
Elvis is working on Ethan's computer,
正在下载全部被盗文件
downloading all the stolen files.
应该问问他
Should check with him.
继续挖掘Damon的信息
Keep digging into Damon.
查清他追踪的东西后 我们就会找到他
We find out what he was after, we find him.
另外 嗨
And, hey.
不论邮件里说了什么
No matter what any e-mails say,
我们首先是一个队伍
we're a team first.
我们互相支持 对吗
We got each other's backs, right?
-是啊 -那必须的
- Yeah. - Totally.
我们很好 King
We're good, King.
带着这股热情去工作吧
Got to work on that enthusiasm.
有什么进展 Elvis
How you doing here, Elvis?
我很火大
I'm pissed.
我是说 Ethan是个混球
I mean, Ethan was a son of a bitch.
他傲慢 他有权傲慢
He was arrogant, he was entitled,
他认为可以凭他一己之力开启世界的无政府状态
he thought he could start world anarchy all by himself.
但他不应该这样死去
But he did not deserve to die this way.
-我是说 这是个耻辱 -Ethan自己做的决定
- I mean, it's humiliating. - Ethan made his own choices.
-这不是你的错 -不是吗
- That's not on you. - No?
我刚认识他的时候
When I met him,
他是个专业游戏测试员 好吗
he was a professional game tester, all right?
我才是那个给他灌输这些思想的人
I'm the one that put all those ideas into his head.
好吧
Okay.
那让我们找出这个凶手
Then let's find his killer.
你找到什么了
What have you learned?
不太多
Not much.
我给这台电脑进行了全面搜查
I gave his computer a full cavity search.
发现了成千上万的机密文件
I found hundreds of thousands of classified files.
但我都不知道从哪儿开始
But I wouldn't even know where to start.
好吧 坐下 Elvis
O-Okay. Sit down, Elvis.
我们从 呃 Damon Yang开始
Let's start with, uh, Damon Yang.
七鹰三合会成员
Seven Eagles Triad member,
可能要对全部五起谋杀案负责
probably responsible for all five murders.
没有Damon Yang的任何信息
I got nothing on Damon Yang.
但是那里有一个Derek Yang
But there is a Derek Yang.
Damon的父亲
Damon's father.
前三合会领导人
Former Triad leader.
他被逮捕 正在等待审判
He was arrested and is awaiting trial.
是的 他被逮捕了
Yes, he was arrested.
但是没有审判 Dwayne
But there was no trial, Dwayne.
我看到不同的文件
These are different files that I'm looking at.
三重加密 安全性极高
Triple encrypted, super secure.
当然 Ethan破解了它
Of course Ethan broke the code.
这可能就是Damon需要他的原因
That's probably why Damon needed him.
文件里面说什么
What do the files say?
文件说 Derek跟中亚地区
It says that, uh, Derek had ties
一些很危险的激进组织有关联
to some pretty nasty radical groups in Central Asia.
所以CIA觉得他可能很有价值
So the CIA decided that he could be a valuable asset.
他们在起诉前 把他从那个国家转移出来
And they whisked him out of the country before the indictment.
非常规引渡
Extraordinary Rendition.
没说他被带到哪儿去了
Does it say where he was taken?
没说 是个秘密行动
No, it's a black site.
但是他们确实给出了审讯他的
But they do give the name of the clandestine operative
秘密特工的名字
that interrogated him.
Jordan Harper
Jordan Harper.
没错 他住在路易斯安那州
Yeah, and he lives in a cabin
一个荒郊野岭的小木屋里
in the middle of nowhere, Louisiana.
Damon想通过追踪Harper来找他的父亲
Damon's going after Harper to find his father.
没错 而且他已经抢先了一步 所以你最好快点
Right, and he's got a head start on you, so you better hurry.
Harper还是没接电话
Harper's still not answering his phone.
派去调查他的州警有消息没
Any word from the state troopers we sent to check up on him?
他们也没接电话
They aren't picking up, either.
这可不好
This isn't good.
Damon Yang可能已经到那里了
Damon Yang could be there already.
但是Damon需要Harper
But Damon needs Harper alive
活着告诉他 他父亲在哪里
to tell him where his father is.
这给了我们一次战斗的机会
So it gives us a fighting chance.
沿这条路还得50分钟才能到小木屋
Cabin's 50 minutes up this road.
我们快没时间了
We're running out of time.
没错 但是如果我们开着全地形车穿过树林
Yeah, but if we take the ATV through the woods,
就能在30分钟之内到达 我们开工
we'll be there in less than 30. Let's do it.
可以出发了
You're good to go.
我们走吧
Let's roll.
两人死亡 是州警
Two dead, troopers.
找到Harper了 没看见Damon
I see Harper. No sign of Damon.
他一定在这附近
Well, he's got to be here somewhere.
行动
Let's move.
Damon Yang
Damon Yang!
NCIS 你无处可逃
NCIS! You got nowhere to run!
我想我们会同归于尽
Then I guess we'll all die here together!
Damon 听着
Damon, listen,
我们都想和平解决
we all want to end this peacefully.
听着 现在还没人受伤 放下武器
Look, no one has to get hurt. Just put down your weapon,
让我们接走Harper
and let us have Harper.
你们想要他 来接他啊
You want him? Come and get him.
-你们在哪呢 -还有十分钟到 怎么了
- Where you guys at? - Ten minutes out. What's up?
我们被压制正在交火
We're pinned down and we're taking fire.
Damon把Harper放在屋里做肉盾
Damon's got Harper barricaded in the cabin.
我们需要找个路线冲进去
We need a way in.
那个小木屋可是生存主义者梦寐以求的房子
That cabin is a survivalist's dream house.
墙壁加厚 电力和安全系统是
Walls are fortified, electricity and security system run on
隔绝互联网的专用网络系统
their own dedicated network off the grid.
我是说 如果他不让你进去 你是进不去的
I mean, if he doesn't want you in, you're not getting in.
-也许吧 也许不是 -来点有用的 伙计们
- Maybe, but maybe not. - Give me something, guys!
要我说 我们用Ethan Beck对付我们的伎俩来对付小木屋
I'm say we do to that cabin what Ethan Beck did to us.
你要黑进他的系统吗
You're gonna hack the system?
我来设定一个病毒去感染小木屋的专用网络
I'm setting up a virus to infect the cabin's dedicated network.
在系统重启之前 应该能给你们
That should give you guys about 90 seconds
大约90秒的时间
before the system reboots.
不管你要做什么 尽快去做
Whatever you do, do it fast.
老兄 你像在看达芬奇
Man, it's like watching da Vinci.
再说一次 很怪异
Again, creepy.
最后一次机会 告诉我
Last chance to tell me
他们把我父亲关在哪儿了
where they're keeping my father.
好了 伙计们
Okay, guys.
停电啦
Here goes nothing.
你和Harper待在一起 我去追Damon
You stay with Harper! I'm getting Damon!
立即放下武器
Put the weapon down now!
无路可走了 Damon
No where to go, Damon.
你被包围了
We got you covered!
说实话 没有任何借口
Honestly, there are no excuses.
我做过一些错误的决定
I made some bad choices.
我并不以此为荣
And I'm not proud of them.
你看 Amy 我也是人
Look, Amy, I'm human.
跟任何人一样 并不完美
Flawed like anyone.
但你知道我还有什么感受吗 感激
But you know what else I am? Grateful.
我感激自己能向NCIS提供有价值的协助
That I was able to provide valuable assistance to NCIS
在更多人受到伤害之前
and put an end to this madness
解决了这堆烂摊子
before anyone else got hurt.
哦 英雄Hamilton
Oh, Hamilton the hero.
真是狡猾
What a snake.
他会毫发无损地从这件事中抽身而出
He's gonna walk away from this whole thing unscathed.
你这么想吗
You think so?
哦 我知道那种语气 Dwayne
Ooh, I know that tone, Dwayne.
你和市长较量过几回合
You've gone a few rounds with the mayor,
对吧
haven't you?
还有好几个回合要进行呢
And I have a few more rounds left to go.
好啊 兄弟
Well, brother,
如果到了那时候
if the time ever comes,
我会很乐意帮你给那个小人做点记号
I'd love to help you take that creep down a notch or three.
现在 我要走了
Until then, I'm out of here.
走前不一起喝个离别酒吗
Leaving without a good-bye drink?
哦 我计划离开时扫荡了你的酒柜
Oh, I raided your cabinet when I was planning my exit.
什么 至少来趟酒吧
What? At least come down
好吗 跟团队一起庆祝一下
to the bar, all right? Celebrate with the team.
来吧
Come on.
团队 团队是你的风格 老兄
Team? Team is your thing, my friend.
我不是这样
My thing is different.
顺便 我会给你的人发点儿东西
By the way, I'm sending your people a little something
好让你们记住我
to remember me by.
哦 这听起来不是什么好事
Well, that sounds ominous.
不会的
Nah.
只是用我的方式来表达谢意
It's just my way of saying thank you.
不用送我 老兄
Stay frosty, my friend.
♪ Yeah, on what you're starting to doubt ♪
♪ So you could give me all you got ♪
♪ You could throw it all at me ♪
♪ Never, ever, ever gonna stop till I'm free ♪
♪ I'm sticking to my guns ♪
♪ Till my work is done ♪
怎样了 伙计们
What's up, party people?
谁准备好庆祝我作为探员的第一个案子 啊哈
Who's ready to celebrate my first case as an agent, huh?
♪ Till my work is done ♪
好吧 今晚 今晚会很疯狂
Yeah, it's gonna be a... gonna be a crazy night.
怎么还来
Not again.
为什么我们还会收到邮件
Why are we still getting e-mails?
案子都结束了
This case is over.
对啊 我们好不容易挺了过来
Yeah, we've already been through this.
我们已经相互道歉过了 真烦人
We've apologized to each other ad nauseam.
听着 对我们最好的解决方案
Look, the best solution is for us all to agree
就是清空它们
to erase them all
看都别看
without looking at them.
-我觉得这是个好主意 -好的
- I think that's a great idea. - Okay.
哦 等等
Oh, wait.
这些不一样
These are different.
哦 没错 这些邮件很好
Oh, yeah, these are nice.
Gregorio 真感人
Gregorio, that's so sweet.
你认为能从我身上学到很多
You think you can learn a lot from me?
别让我变得多愁善感 好吗
Don't go getting mushy on me, okay?
我猜你们收到了Elvis的道别礼物
I'm guessing you received Elvis' good-bye present.
他一定重新编程了幸灾乐祸算法
He must've reverse engineered the schadenfreude algorithm
只搜索我们写过的
to only search out the good things
关于彼此的好话
we wrote about each other.
而且我觉得这些好话远多于之前的坏话
Which I am sure far outnumbered the bad.
好了
All right.
进入正题
Let's get down to business.
敬Sebastian
Here's to Sebastian
你完成了你的第一个案子
for getting through your first case
还受了一点伤
with minimal injuries.
-干得漂亮 亲爱的 -敬Sebastian
- Well done, dear. - To Sebastian!
♪ Till my work is done. ♪